{
    "subject": "Steven_E._de_Souza",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Arnold's_Wrecking_Co.",
    "human_readable": "Steven E. de Souza created Arnold's Wrecking Co.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9311074614524841,
            "question": "Who created Arnold's Wrecking Co?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8771447539329529,
            "question": "When was Arnold's Wrecking Co. created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7970237731933594,
            "question": "What is the name of the company created by Steven E. de Souza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7906650900840759,
            "question": "Who is Steven E. de Souza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7182187438011169,
            "question": "What other companies has Steven E. de Souza created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7161034345626831,
            "question": "Where is Arnold's Wrecking Co. located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7156989574432373,
            "question": "What type of company is Arnold's Wrecking Co.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.712715744972229,
            "question": "Is Arnold's Wrecking Co. a real company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6667473912239075,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the employees of Arnold's Wrecking Co.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6151720881462097,
            "question": "What services does Arnold's Wrecking Co. provide?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Steven E. de Souza created Arnold's Wrecking Co.",
            "html": "yago_7858_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about the employees of Arnold's Wrecking Co.?",
            "html": "yago_7858_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Arnold's Wrecking Co. a real company?",
            "html": "yago_7858_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of company is Arnold's Wrecking Co.?",
            "html": "yago_7858_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7858_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7858_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7858_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7858_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7858_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7858_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7858_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7858_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7858_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7858_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that \"Written by, directed by and starring Die Hard and Commando scribe Steven De Souza, Arnold's Wrecking Company follows three friends as they go into the marijuana business fulltime...\"  This indicates Steven E. de Souza created the film."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there are multiple documents mentioning Steven E. de Souza and his work as a writer or screenwriter, but none of them mention him creating Arnold's Wrecking Co. The document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_7858/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt is actually about the movie Arnold's Wrecking Co., and it describes the plot, but does not credit Steven E. de Souza as its creator."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Steven E. de Souza wrote the screenplay for \"Arnold's Wrecking Company,\" which supports the statement that Steven E. de Souza created (wrote) Arnold's Wrecking Co."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Steven E. de Souza wrote Arnold's Wrecking Company, but the context information suggests that he also directed and starred in it. The film's plot, tone, and style are described as being consistent with the era of his other notable works, such as Die Hard and Commando, which were written by him.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}